Guide to the Jim Fouratt Papers
Fouratt (Jim) Papers
- Band demos and recordings, 1980 1989; Series IV; 77.42 Linear Feet; (78 boxes); 1347 Audiocassettes; 7 Audiotape Reels
  - Aura, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:11:44 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Static is present. The program is muffled at times. (Box 79, Item barcode 39002140906455)
  - Mikel Rouse Broken Consort, 1985 April 7; 1 Audiocassette; 00:34:40 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. (Box 79, Item barcode 39002140906463)
  - Terese Gunn Group, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:19:51 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. (Box 79, Item barcode 39002140906471)
  - The Source, Insect Surfers, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:52:49 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. (Box 79, Item barcode 39002140906489)
  - Delphine Blue, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 01:00:41 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Static and dropouts in the audio are present. (Box 79, Item barcode 39002140906497)
  - Peter Taylor, 1978; 1 Audiocassette; 00:22:19 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Dropouts in the audio are present. (Box 79, Item barcode 39002140906505)
  - Volunteers, 1982; 1 Audiocassette; 00:07:07 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. (Box 79, Item barcode 39002140906513)
  - ISM CBGB, 1982 March 14; 1 Audiocassette; 00:36:09 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Static is present. The program is in silence from 00:20:06-00:20:29. (Box 79, Item barcode 39002140906521)
  - Pack Nine, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:39:33 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Static is present. The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. (Box 79, Item barcode 39002140906539)
  - Frank Bednash, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:10:08 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. (Box 79, Item barcode 39002140906547)
  - The Satin Latins, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:30:25 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Static is preent. (Box 79, Item barcode 39002140906554)
  - Contractions, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:11:22 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. (Box 79, Item barcode 39002140906562)
  - Joey Joey, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:12:19 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 79, Item barcode 39002140906570)
  - Hypertension, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:11:38 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorte at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. (Box 79, Item barcode 39002140906588)
  - Jim's Resp. To (?), 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 01:34:32 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted. Static and dropouts in the audio are present. Volume fluctuations are present. The program is unintelligible at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Speed fluctuations are present. (Box 79, Item barcode 39002140906596)
  - Lightnin Harry Dee, 1982; 1 Audiocassette; 00:14:52 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Static is present. Dropouts in the audio are present. (Box 79, Item barcode 39002140906604)
  - Ryo Kawasaki & The Golden Dragon, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:54:32 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. The program is muffled. (Box 79, Item barcode 39002140906620)
  - The Necropolitans, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:11:34 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. (Box 79, Item barcode 39002140906612)
  - Tirez Tirez, 1980 1989 (Box 81)
  - Tirez Tirez - Story Of The Year, 1980 1989 (Box 81)
  - Pylon @ Maxwells, 1980 1989 (Box 81)
  - Pylon @ 123 Club, 1980 1989 (Box 81)
  - Pylon - live, 1980 1989 (Box 81)
  - Pylon, 1980 1989 (Box 81)
  - Pylon, 1980 1989 (Box 81)
  - CBGB's - live, Richard Lloyd, 1980 1989 (Box 81)
  - Tirez Tirez - Under The Door, 1980 1989 (Box 81)
  - Mikel Rouse Broken Consort, 1980 1989 (Box 81)
  - Tirez Tirez - Story Of The Year, 1980 1989 (Box 81)
  - Tirez Tirez, Broken Consort, 1980 1989 (Box 81)
  - Tirez Tirez - Story Of The Year, 1980 1989 (Box 81)
  - Mikel Rouse - Quorum, 1980 1989 (Box 81)
  - Tirez Tirez - My Mistake, 1980 1989 (Box 81)
  - Mikel Rouse Broken Consort, 1980 1989 (Box 81)
  - Mikel Rouse, 1980 1989 (Box 81)
  - The Toasters, 1980 1989 (Box 82)
  - Mama Quilla II, 1980 1989 (Box 82)
  - Ministry, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:34:43 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio distortion, hiss and hum are present. (Box 82, Item barcode 39002141025602)
  - Angel and the Drunken Gods, 1980 1989 (Box 82)
  - R.E.M. - demo, 1980 1989 (Box 82)
  - R.E.M. - rough mixes, 1980 1989 (Box 82)
  - Ornette Coleman, 1980 1989 (Box 82)
  - Julie Heyward, 1980 1989 (Box 82)
  - Clinic Q, 1980 1989 (Box 82)
  - In The Vines, 1980 1989 (Box 82)
  - Tirez Tirez, 1980 1989 (Box 82)
  - Mikel Rouse, 1980 1989 (Box 82)
  - Living, 1980 1989 (Box 82)
  - Mikel Rouse Broken Consort - A Walk in the Woods, 1980 1989 (Box 82)
  - Tirez Tirez - Social Responsibility, 1980 1989 (Box 82)
  - Tirez Tirez - Social Responsibility, 1980 1989 (Box 82)
  - Mikel Rouse, 1980 1989 (Box 82)
  - Mikel Rouse, 1980 1989 (Box 82)
  - Phranc, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:46:45 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Dropouts in the audio are present. (Box 83, Item barcode 39002141024043)
  - Michael Callen, Purple Heart, 1980 1989; This is a commerical tape. It has not been digitized. (Box 83)
  - Martin + Biello Songs, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:32:03 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Dropouts in the audio are present. (Box 83, Item barcode 39002141024050)
  - Jan Corliss, 1988; 1 Audiocassette; 00:12:42 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Dropouts in the audio are present. (Box 83, Item barcode 39002141024068)
  - Michael Callen - Healin, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:09:42 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Dropouts in the audio are present. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. (Box 83, Item barcode 39002141024076)
  - Helen Hooke, 1984; 1 Audiocassette; 00:07:08 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Dropouts in the audio are present. (Box 83, Item barcode 39002141024084)
  - Michael Callen, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:21:07 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Dropouts in the audio are present. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. (Box 83, Item barcode 39002141024092)
  - Boys Life, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:30:56 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is muffled at times. Dropouts in the audio are present. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. (Box 83, Item barcode 39002141024100)
  - Lowlife, 1984 1985; 1 Audiocassette; 00:17:41 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Dropouts in the audio are present. (Box 83, Item barcode 39002141024118)
  - Science, 1984; 00:21:00 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); 1 Audiocassette; The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Dropouts can be heard on the program. (Box 83, Item barcode 39002141024126)
  - Painty Adore, undated; 00:14:43 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Static is present. High background noise is present. Dropouts in the audio are present. (Box 83, Item barcode 39002141024134)
  - Frank Maya + Decals, 1978 1979; 1 Audiocassette; 00:12:20 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Static is present. Dropouts in the program are present. Overlapping content can be heard. The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Channel audio is unbalanced. (Box 83, Item barcode 39002141024142)
  - Hot Lunch / Deadboys, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:47:02 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio distortion, hum, and hiss are present. (Box 83, Item barcode 39002141023441)
  - Boys Brigade, 1981 December 9; 1 Audiocassette; 00:24:47 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Dropouts in the audio casn be heard. (Box 83, Item barcode 39002141024159)
  - Dub Wrestlers, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:22:08 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Dropouts in the audio are present. (Box 83, Item barcode 39002141024167)
  - Zette, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:34:14 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Dropouts in the audio are present. (Box 83, Item barcode 39002141024175)
  - Tiny Desk Unit, 1980 February 3 1980 February 4; 1 Audiocassette; 00:38:56 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Dropouts in the audio are present. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. Audio is unbalanced. (Box 83, Item barcode 39002141024183)
  - Pal Shazar, 1980 1989 (Box 84)
  - Polyrock, 1980 1989 (Box 84)
  - Time Twins, 1980 1989 (Box 84)
  - Lari Soks, 1980 1989 (Box 84)
  - Lowlife - EP, 1980 1989 (Box 84)
  - Michael Callen - Purple Heart, 1980 1989 (Box 84)
  - Science, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:25:27 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. The program is in silence from 00:24:22-00:24:56. (Box 84, Item barcode 39002141025610)
  - Visage, 1980 1989 (Box 84)
  - Fetchin Bones, 1980 1989 (Box 84)
  - Tuxedo Moon, 1980 1989 (Box 84)
  - Esmerelda, 1980 1989 (Box 84)
  - Satin Latins, 1980 1989 (Box 84)
  - Diamanda Galas, 1980 1989 (Box 84)
  - Strange Party, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:04:19 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audiovisual material: Restricted fragile. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.; Audio distortion, hum, and hiss are present. (Box 84, Item barcode 39002140952285)
  - Arsenal, 1980 1989 (Box 84)
  - Jeff: Jane Hudson, 1980 1989 (Box 84)
  - The Ordinaires, 1980 1989 (Box 84)
  - Zabawny, 1980 1989 (Box 84)
  - Douches Bain DJ, 1981 September 11; 1 Audiocassette; 01:33:37 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Dropouts in the audio are present. The program is muffled at times. Speed fluctuations are present. Static, clicks, and pops can be heard. (Box 85, Item barcode 39002137159050)
  - Chris Lopez DJ, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 01:34:43 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Static, clicks and pops are present. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. (Box 85, Item barcode 39002137159043)
  - Tim Warren, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 01:08:53 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Static is present. The program is distorted at times. (Box 85, Item barcode 39002137159035)
  - DJ - Danceteria, Derek Freedman, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:53:05 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Static and high amounts of hum are present. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. (Box 85, Item barcode 39002137159027)
  - Ornette Coleman, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 01:35:55 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. Static is present An echo can be heard at times. (Box 85, Item barcode 39002137159019)
  - Lounge Lizards, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:29:16 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio is distorted. Hum and hiss can be heard. The program starts and ends abruptly. (Box 85, Item barcode 39002137158896)
  - Sinatras, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:06:29 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Static is present. (Box 85, Item barcode 39002137159001)
  - Indoor Life, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:18:51 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times sounds hollow or unclear. (Box 85, Item barcode 39002137158995)
  - The Orchids, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:07:04 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Static can be heard. (Box 85, Item barcode 39002137158987)
  - V/A "I Love My Voice", 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:38:42 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Dropouts in the audio are present. Static can be heard. (Box 85, Item barcode 39002137158979)
  - Paul Hallasy DJ, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 01:02:23 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Static and dropouts in the audio are present. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. (Box 85, Item barcode 39002137158961)
  - Poets: Will Bennett, George Therese Dickenson, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:33:57 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Static and dropouts in the program are present. Speed fluctuations are present. The program is in silence from 00:05:47-00:26:38. (Box 85, Item barcode 39002137158953)
  - Peter Dayton Band, 1983; 1 Audiocassette; 00:14:16 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Static is present. (Box 85, Item barcode 39002137158946)
  - Arsenal, 1987 January 23; 1 Audiocassette; 00:12:53 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Dropouts and static can be heard. The program is muffled at times. (Box 85, Item barcode 39002137158938)
  - Michael Callen - Songs for the AIDies, 1987; 1 Audiocassette; 00:18:43 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Static is present. An echo, at times, can be heard on the tape. (Box 85, Item barcode 39002137158920)
  - Michael Callen - Living in Wartime, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:17:26 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Static is present. Dropouts in the audio are present. An echo, at times, can be heard on the tape. (Box 85, Item barcode 39002137158912)
  - Lowlife, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:14:13 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Static is present. (Box 85, Item barcode 39002137158904)
  - The Must, 1980 1989 (Box 86)
  - Helot Revolt, 1980 1989 (Box 86)
  - Kongress, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:02:31 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); There is an echo at the start of the tape. Audio is distorted. Audio hiss and hum can be heard. (Box 86, Item barcode 39002140901431)
  - Hagatha, 1980 1989 (Box 86)
  - Daniel Johnston, 1980 1989 (Box 86)
  - Soldier String Quartet, 1980 1989 (Box 86)
  - Tamela Glenn, 1980 1989 (Box 86)
  - The Pop Tarts, 1980 1989 (Box 86)
  - Go Van Go, 1980 1989 (Box 86)
  - Junior Vasquez, 1980 1989 (Box 86)
  - Shoulders, 1980 1989 (Box 86)
  - Clinic Q, 1980 1989 (Box 86)
  - New Order, 1980 1989 (Box 86)
  - Annie Golden, 1980 1989 (Box 86)
  - O. Boy, 1980 1989 (Box 86)
  - Joe Rusnak DJ #1, 1980 1989 (Box 86)
  - Joe Rusnak DJ #2, 1980 1989 (Box 86)
  - Brian's Christmas Tape, 1980 1989 (Box 86)
  - The Everglades, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:15:11 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio hum, hiss, and distortion is present. (Box 87, Item barcode 39002140951139)
  - Jeff Hudson, 1980 1989 (Box 87)
  - August Darnell, 1980 1989 (Box 87)
  - Love Men, 1980 1989 (Box 87)
  - Linda Hudes Power Trio, 1980 1989 (Box 87)
  - Linda Hudes Power Trio, 1980 1989 (Box 87)
  - The Raybeats, 1980 1989 (Box 87)
  - lesley woods, 1980 1989 (Box 87)
  - John Outlaw, 1980 1989 (Box 87)
  - Daniel Johnston, 1980 1989 (Box 87)
  - Daniel Johnston, 1980 1989 (Box 87)
  - Miracle Room, 1980 1989 (Box 87)
  - Prairie Fire, 1980 1989 (Box 87)
  - New York Samba Band, 1980 1989 (Box 87)
  - Pig Bag, 1980 1989 (Box 87)
  - No Sisters demo, 1980 1989 (Box 87)
  - War 8, 1980 1989 (Box 87)
  - R.E.M. cassette set, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 88, Item barcode 39002141027772)
  - Jim Fouratt's Penguin Nights, preview compilation master, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 88, Item barcode 39002141027764)
  - Hot Lunch, 1977 November 30; 1 Audiocassette; 01:24:39 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Unbalanced audio. Audio is low in the left channel. Audio distortion, hum, and hiss. (Box 88, Item barcode 39002141020710)
  - Catholic Girls, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 88, Item barcode 39002141027756)
  - Partyline, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 88, Item barcode 39002141027749)
  - Zo-Reller, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 88, Item barcode 39002141027731)
  - "SicKids", 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 88, Item barcode 39002141027723)
  - Factual, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 88, Item barcode 39002141027715)
  - Nelson Ferrer Band, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 88, Item barcode 39002141027707)
  - The Overnights, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 88, Item barcode 39002141027699)
  - Open City, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 88, Item barcode 39002141027681)
  - WKGB, 1979 1981; 1 Audiocassette (Box 88, Item barcode 39002141027673)
  - Stickmen, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 88, Item barcode 39002141027665)
  - Terrorists, 1979; 1 Audiocassette (Box 88, Item barcode 39002141027657)
  - The Units, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 88, Item barcode 39002141027640)
  - The Units, 1979; 1 Audiocassette (Box 88, Item barcode 39002141027632)
    Songs include:
    Japan
    I Am Sorry
    Blue Car
  - Isolation, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 88, Item barcode 39002141027624)
  - Tellus #8, 1980 1989 (Box 89)
  - Tellus #7, 1980 1989 (Box 89)
  - Tellus #11, 1980 1989 (Box 89)
  - Tellus #14, 1980 1989 (Box 89)
  - Tellus #13, 1980 1989 (Box 89)
  - Tellus #12, 1980 1989 (Box 89)
  - Tellus #10, 1980 1989 (Box 89)
  - Tellus #9, 1980 1989 (Box 89)
  - The Dragons, 1980 1989 (Box 89)
  - Carboy, 1980 1989 (Box 89)
  - Hand Over Fist, 1980 1989 (Box 89)
  - Mary Kelley & Friends, 1980 1989 (Box 89)
  - Kitsch, 1980 1989 (Box 89)
  - Norman Salant Group, 1980 1989 (Box 89)
  - Verbal Drama, 1980 1989 (Box 89)
  - Dresden Danse, 1980 1989 (Box 89)
  - Al Jourgensen - The Ministry, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:26:11 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio distortion, hiss, and hum are present. (Box 89, Item barcode 39002140950545)
  - Taller / Sedition / Glass, 1980 1989 (Box 90)
  - The Units, 1980 1989 (Box 90)
  - Anna Bouboula, 1980 1989 (Box 90)
  - Comboland 1, 1980 1989 (Box 90)
  - Comboland 2, 1980 1989 (Box 90)
  - Comboland 3, 1980 1989 (Box 90)
  - The Pseudos, 1980 1989 (Box 90)
  - Bagdads, 1980 1989 (Box 90)
  - The Scene, 1980 1989 (Box 90)
  - The Symptoms, 1980 1989 (Box 90)
  - Playgroup, 1980 1989 (Box 90)
  - Cheeky, 1980 1989 (Box 90)
  - Skin, 1980 1989 (Box 90)
  - Wind at Night, 1980 1989 (Box 90)
  - The Other, 1980 1989 (Box 90)
  - Those Foolish Things, 1980 1989 (Box 90)
  - Wind at Night, 1980 1989 (Box 90)
  - Cadre 8, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 91, Item barcode 39002141027921)
  - The Vipers, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 91, Item barcode 39002141027913)
  - Pickett, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 91, Item barcode 39002141027905)
  - Young Snakes, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 91, Item barcode 39002141027897)
  - Donna Cornell (EMPTY), 1980 1989 (Box 91)
  - Montonson, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 91, Item barcode 39002141027889)
  - NC Acts, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 91, Item barcode 39002141027871)
  - Rorschach, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 91, Item barcode 39002141027863)
  - Electra sampler, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 91, Item barcode 39002141027855)
  - Spoil, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 91, Item barcode 39002141027848)
  - Jump Up, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 91, Item barcode 39002141027830)
  - City Beat, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 91, Item barcode 39002141027822)
  - David E. Williams, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 91, Item barcode 39002141027814)
  - Malabou Dolphins, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 91, Item barcode 39002141027806)
  - Kitsch, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 91, Item barcode 39002141027798)
  - Health Hen, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:12:13 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Static is present. The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Audio is unbalanced from 11:52 until the end. (Box 91, Item barcode 39002141027780)
  - The Affectives, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:09:37 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 91, Item barcode 39002141027616)
  - Wild Ones, 1980 1989 (Box 92)
  - Dancing Cigarettes, 1980 1989 (Box 92)
  - King Trigger, 1980 1989 (Box 92)
  - She's So, Rose Lesniak, 1980 1989 (Box 92)
  - Hoy Boy & The Doys, 1980 1989 (Box 92)
  - Mother May I, 1980 1989 (Box 92)
  - Giant Ears Listen In At Dawn, Radio Moscow, 1980 1989 (Box 92)
  - Fresh Sounds from Middle America, 1980 1989 (Box 92)
  - The Everglades, 1980 1989 (Box 92)
  - Bralt, 1980 1989 (Box 92)
  - Local Noise Organization, 1980 1989 (Box 92)
  - Clean Heat, 1980 1989 (Box 92)
  - Dangerous Club, 1980 1989 (Box 92)
  - Actual Size, 1980 1989 (Box 92)
  - Kammer Musik, 1980 1989 (Box 92)
  - Dance Part II - AVINS, 1980 1989 (Box 92)
  - Uzi, 1980 1989 (Box 92)
  - Lisa of the Lost, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:14:28 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audiovisual material: Restricted fragile. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.; Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. (Box 93, Item barcode 39002141023631)
  - Wild Ones, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:18:49 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. (Box 93, Item barcode 39002141023649)
  - J.A. Deane - Solo Trombone, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:32:32 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Static is present. (Box 93, Item barcode 39002141023656)
  - Zone, rehearsal demo, 1985; 1 Audiocassette; 00:17:25 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. (Box 93, Item barcode 39002141023664)
  - Zone, 1984; 1 Audiocassette; 00:10:17 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 93, Item barcode 39002141023672)
  - J.D. demo, 1983 April 25; 1 Audiocassette; 01:32:54 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. There is a warble in the beginning of the program. Static is present. The tape winds during the program. (Box 93, Item barcode 39002141023680)
  - Wind at Night, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:16:45 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Dropouts in the audio are present. (Box 93, Item barcode 39002141023698)
  - Richard Lloyd - Black to White, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:03:12 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. (Box 93, Item barcode 39002141023706)
  - World Pablo Laprelle, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:13:59 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. Tape can be heard winding during program around 00:09:30. Volume decreases around 00:09:00 until the end of the program. (Box 93, Item barcode 39002141023714)
  - Frank Jargon & The Photo Opportunity, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:18:36 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. (Box 93, Item barcode 39002141023722)
  - NNB demo, Powerclown Music, 1980; 1 Audiocassette; 00:15:06 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio hiss, distortion, and hum are present. (Box 93, Item barcode 39002140905267)
  - Axual Fax, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:11:57 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. (Box 93, Item barcode 39002141023730)